[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 10]
Although we just met not long ago,
we share
the same desire to survive.
Spill it.
What's the matter?
I'm just trying to tell you
that there is a mole among us.
Who is it?
I'm not entirely sure who it is yet,
but I have a way to find her out.
Why should I believe you?
Giving it a try won't harm you.
The thing is, if we don't root her out,
we might all be doomed
in tomorrow's death match.
Miss Nan,
you're so smart.
Wan,
how about we just skip the talk?
For once, I finally had the mood to play
a guessing game with you girls.
Little did I expect
my identity would be revealed so soon.
You do know how to enjoy yourself,
Lord Voice-Keeper,
for joining a death match yourself.
I wonder if you will jump
into the den of snakes
the same when you lose?
Guards!
Hold on.
Just now, you claimed to bet the lives
of all the female prisoners here
on the third round.
Are you aware
how high the stakes are?
Our plan is to take a gamble.
Fine.
Then tell me.
How do you want to proceed
with the third round?
Both of us will each roll a dice and guess
the other's number after the dices land.
Whoever guesses correctly wins.
One game decides it all.
What do you say?
I agree.
Let's do as you said.
This is the third round
of the current death match.
Ladies,
please get ready.
If Miss Nan loses,
we'll have to die with her.
If you're that worried,
go play the game yourselves.
Will Yanzhi win?
Stop with this.
No more rubbing.
My palms are already sweating.
Ladies, get ready.
The final round of this death match
begins now.
If the plan can be carried out at the end,
I hope you will help me with your ability
to tell dice numbers
by sound.
Why should I help you?
You also long to leave this place,
don't you?
I suppose it takes more than
an individual's effort
to win the voice-keeper.
Only by working together
do we stand a chance of victory.
We are hardly friends.
Why would you trust me?
We will be friends after this.
I firmly believe we will all get out
of here at last.
After I identify the dice number,
I'll tell you what it is
by blinking my eyes.
Sorry.
I guess the number of your dice...
is one.
What now?
Have you lost your ability to speak
like the mute servant?
She already waived her turn to guess.
Why don't you announce the result now?
The winner of the third round
is Nan Yanzhi.
Take them down!
What?
Are you going back on your word now?
Wan,
you could've defeated her.
Why did you deliberately let her go?
To err is human.
I misheard her dice this time.
But I've never seen you err before.
Does this have something to do
with Zhuang Wujiu again?
Wan,
previously, you were deceived by her
and made a grave mistake already.
How could you recklessly believe her again
and take one more wrong step?
We must not break
the rules of death matchs.
But have you thought about...
Zan,
I've made up my mind.
It never occurred to me
that the great Lord Voice-Keeper
would break her word.
It's impossible to let you
take everyone away.
However,
we can give you some gold
so you can reach the fourth floor
effortlessly.
I must take all the girls away.
Don't push your luck!
Zan,
please leave the room.
I'd like a word with her in private.
Wan...
I'm asking you to leave.
Tell me.
Why do you insist on
taking all the girls with you
and refuse to leave by yourself?
Because I've made them a promise
that I'd get them out of here with me.
What did you just say?
A promise?
Ha-ha.
You don't actually believe
that sort of stuff, do you?
Why wouldn't I?
The night is still young.
How about...
I tell you a story?
Ten years ago,
in the Moon House,
there was a famous courtesan
with unmatched pipa skills in the capital.
Coincidentally,
she was also called Ms. Kou.
All I seek in my life
is to spend every day
playing musical instruments with you
harmoniously
like this.
May our happiness last forever.
May our bond never fade from memory.
Blessed to be with a beauty like you,
I promise to stay committed
to you for a lifetime.
Hearing your words,
I feel
so fortunate.
Ms. Kou!
Mr. Xie...
Mr. Xie was taken by the authorities!
How did that happen?
Mr. Xie is said to be
engaged in the rebellion
conspired by Prince Xu and his aides.
Prince Xu's matter involves many people.
I must rescue Xie.
Take these.
If the money is still not enough,
then...
Then pawn this pipa.
Ms. Kou,
this red sandalwood pipa
is your most precious possession.
What pipa will you use if this is gone?
There's no time to worry about that now.
-Do as I said and go.
-Kou Wan!
We're ordered to arrest Kou Wan,
an accomplice
to a rebel surnamed Xie.
Ms. Kou, you'll have to go with us.